subsea7.com 2019-08-03

# Privacy & Cookies

This is the privacy statement for Subsea 7’s website (https://www.subsea7.com/en/index.html). At Subsea 7 (“Subsea 7” or “we” or “our”), we want you to feel secure when visiting our website and are committed to maintaining your trust and privacy.

Your data will be held and managed by Subsea 7 S.A. (the "Company" and, together with all companies within the Subsea 7 group, including joint ventures, the “Group” or “Subsea 7”).

We will at all times seek to comply with Data Protection Legislation and any applicable laws and regulations to ensure that the personal information you give us is kept secure and treated fairly and lawfully.

### Information we may collect from you and how we use it

We do not collect any personal information about individuals unless it is specifically and knowingly provided by them. If you decide to contact us or make use of personalised services (i.e. when you sign up for our Email Alerts (mailing list), send us an email enquiry via our Contact Form, or apply online for a job vacancy (online application form and career profile)) we collect your personal information and use that information as required for us to provide the relevant services or handle your query. Examples of the private information we may collect include your name, email address, occupation and country. We may use that information to tell you about the company’s latest news and financial information, to communicate with you or share information that you have asked for and to manage your online personal career profile. 

When you visit the site, we also, though the use of cookies and/or other similar technologies, gather information automatically about your browser type, IP address and details of how you accessed the website and the pages you visited. We use this analytical information to help us understand how visitors use the website and make improvements to the layout, content and/or performance of the site. For more information on cookies, please see our cookies section at the end of this Privacy Statement.

### Who do we share your personal data with?

We may store or transfer your personal data to our other Subsea companies around the world. We transfer and store your personal data with security measures in place.

In certain circumstances, we may share your information with selected service providers who perform functions on our behalf such as providing IT, delivering our email alerts and other support and maintenance services that help us run the website. Our service providers will only use your information to the extent necessary to perform their functions.

We have the right to share your information with law enforcement or public authorities if legally required to do so, or to prevent security, fraud or technical issues. 

### Email alerts

If you have registered to receive email updates from us, and you no longer wish to receive these, you can unsubscribe by contacting us or by using the unsubscribe link which is included on all email alerts.

### Security and storage of personal data

We place great importance on the security of all personal information associated with our website users. We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information under our control. Whilst we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of information online, we use all reasonable efforts to protect it.

There are procedures and technologies to maintain the security of personal data from the point of collection to the point of destruction; these controls protect against the unlawful or unauthorised processing, accidental loss of, or damage to, personal data.

You have the right to access information held about you and to request an amendment or removal of such information if necessary.

If you have any questions about the information we hold about you or the way in which your data is being collected or used which are not answered by this Privacy Statement please contact us at dataprotection@subsea7.com.

### How long do we keep your information?

We will only hold your information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes for which it was collected, before making it non-identifiable or deleting it.

If you choose to unsubscribe from a service, we may keep a list containing your personal details so we know you have unsubscribed.

### Applying for a job at Subsea 7?

When you apply to become part of the Subsea 7 team via our careers website and online application form, your information will be processed solely for the purposes in which it is provided and will be retained for a period necessary to comply with our legal and administrative requirements. For more information, please see ‘How to apply and FAQs’. 

### Links to other websites

This Privacy Policy does not cover links within this site linking to other websites. If you follow a link to one of our partners or joint ventures, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and we do not accept responsibility or liability for information supplied to these websites.

### Changes to this Privacy Statement

We keep our Privacy Statement under regular review. This statement was last updated on Monday 21 May 2018.

### Cookies

_What is a cookie?_

Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information that are downloaded to your personal computer, mobile or other device when you first visit a website. The next time you visit that website, any relevant cookies are sent back to the website, so that the site knows you have been there before. Cookies help you to navigate between different website pages efficiently, remembering your preferences and generally improving the user experience.

_Cookies we use_

We use cookies (Performance and Functional) to collect anonymous information about how visitors use the Subsea 7 website. By using our website, you agree to have cookies placed on your personal computer or device. These cookies do not collect information that identifies a visitor and are only used to improve how the website works. Subsea 7 uses cookies to speed navigation, improve functionality and keep track of how visitors use the site, for example, which pages visitors go to most often or how many users are connected to the Subsea 7 site at any one time. We cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.

We use cookies to enhance your experience, but you can disable or delete cookies in your internet browser settings.

_Google Analytics_

When you visit [www.subsea7.com](http://www.subsea7.com/) we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to keep track of the pages you and other visitors have viewed so that we can improve the quality of our website and its content.

Please note that we only use necessary and analytical cookies on our website and do not use cookies for marketing purposes.

If you have any questions about cookies, please contact us via email at [dataprotection@subsea7.com](mailto:dataprotection@subsea7.com).
